Ashleigh Schuldt

801-669-7631

ashleigh.schuldt@gmail.com https://github.com/ashleighschuldt

I'm a self motivated team player with a can-do attitude. I have an extensive background in accounting, but am making the switch to development. I love being challenged by logic statements and math. I have found that excitement again with coding. I love the perpetual challenges that I'm faced with on each new project. I have excellent time management skills and 2+ years of experience working remote with a team to meet deadlines.



EXPERIENCE

Vivint Smart Home, Provo — *Staff Accountant*

June 2014 - PRESENT

- Worked with dev to create new reports and reconciliations for revenue.
- Migrate fixed assets to a new accounting system in 2017 and verify the accuracy of the migration.
- Logically processed out our asset review process to better function with our entries into our SAP system.
- Regularly work in a project environment to track completion and spend of CAPEX projects.
- Work with internal audit to regularly test processes ensuring accuracy and that controls are implemented correctly.

Accelerated Payment Technologies, Pleasant Grove — Staff Accountant

March 2011 - May 2014

- Work with sales to develop more streamlined hardware ordering process.
- Calculate commissions for hardware.
- Work with multiple departments to process expense reports and employee reimbursements.

EDUCATION

DevMountain, Provo — Web Development

November 2017 - July 2018

Utah Valley University, Orem — BS in Accounting

August 2008 - August 2013

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, React.js, Redux, SQL, Postgres, Git, REST, HTTP

Qualifications

Strong written and verbal communication.

Experience with unit testing using Mocha Chai.js and expect.js

Experience working with remote teams and meeting deadlines.

Rapidly master and apply new concepts with excellent comprehension and retention.

Excellent attention to detail.

Understanding of Agile/Scrum and Waterfall methodologies.